Main Page - URL:
https://www.textpad.com/

TextPad® 8.1 is a powerful, general purpose editor for plain text files. Easy to use, with all 
the features a power user requires.
More ... (https://www.textpad.com/products/textpad/index.html)

When just getting the job done is work enough, the last thing you need is to waste time having 
to learn yet another computer application. Your experience with other tools should be relevant 
to each new application, making it possible to sit down and use that new application right 
away.

That's why TextPad® is so popular. Whether you simply need a powerful replacement for Notepad, 
a tool for editing your web pages, or a programming IDE, TextPad does what you want, the way 
you would expect.

It's available from this web site on a try before you buy basis, so please download your trial 
(https://www.textpad.com/download/index.html) copy now, and find out just how productive you 
can be. 


Download Page - URL:
https://www.textpad.com/download/index.html


TextPad 8 Downloads:

User Interface:
English

Online Help/Spelling:
English/American, British & Canadian

Version/Date:
8.1.2/07-Mar-2017

Download:
64-bit - https://www.textpad.com/download/v81/x64/txpeng812-64.zip
32-bit - https://www.textpad.com/download/v81/win32/txpeng812-32.zip


You are welcome to download a copy of TextPad for evaluation, or to upgrade from an earlier 
release. There is no charge for the download, but you must pay for the software if you decide 
to keep it. A single user license costs only £16.50 GBP (approximately $27 USD).

TextPad 7.6 is a free upgrade for existing users, but please read this important information
(https://www.textpad.com/buy/upgrades/info) about upgrading to TextPad 8.

These zipped EXE files contain TextPad, with the English user interface, plus one other 
language, and a dictionary for the spell checker, as shown in the table. (Other dictionaries - 
https://www.textpad.com/download/lexicons.html - may be downloaded separately.) If the online help is not available in a given language, it is 
supplied in English. For your security, all executable files are digitally signed.

